또 다른 문제로 우리는 다양한
단어들을 사용하고 있습니다.
Another problem is that we
often use different words
거의 같은 의미이지만..
to mean almost the same thing.
cat 또는 kitty(고양이새끼)가 있습니다.
You can say cat or you can say kitty.
그 두 단어는 같지 않지만,
거의 비슷한 의미를 갖습니다.
They're not the same, but
they mean similar things.
우리는 정말로 비슷한 물건을 가지고
있다는것을 기억하세요.
Remember that when we have things
that are similar, we really,
그 비슷한 물건 사이에는
parameters가 공유됩니다.
really would like to share
parameters between them.
그러나 kitty는 정확히는
cat과는 다릅니다.
But kitty is completely
different from cat.
그래서, 그것들 사이의 어떤것을
공유하기를 원한다면,
So if we want to share
anything between them.
문서 분류에 대한 것을 배울 것이다.
We're going to have to learn
that they are related.
왜냐하면, 그것들은 deep learning에 대한
매우 비중이 있는 문제들이다.
So that's a very big problem for
deep learning.
중요한 단어를 찾고 싶어합니다.
We'd like to see those
important words often enough
자동적으로 의미를 배우도록
할 수 있도록..
to be able to learn
the meanings automatically.
각각의 단어들의 관계를 배울 수 있도록
하고 싶습니다.
And we'd also like to learn how
words relate to each other so
단어들 사이의 파라메타를 공유해서..
that we can share
parameters between them.
그러나, 이것들은 분류된 데이터를
수집하는 것을 의미합니다.
But that would mean collecting
a lot of label data.
실제로, 분류된 데이터를 그렇게
많이는 필요하지 않습니다.
In fact, it would require
way too much label data for
정말 중요한 작업에 대해서는..
any task that really matters.